{
    "subject": "resource/Dry_well",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Stormwater_management",
    "human_readable": "The subject of Dry well is Stormwater management.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9181855320930481,
            "question": "How does a dry well contribute to stormwater management?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8222798705101013,
            "question": "What are the benefits of using dry wells for stormwater management?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7266736030578613,
            "question": "What is the purpose of stormwater management?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6947017908096313,
            "question": "What other methods can be used for stormwater management besides dry wells?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.634505569934845,
            "question": "Are there any drawbacks to using dry wells for stormwater management?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3609101176261902,
            "question": "Why is effective stormwater management important for urban areas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17798414826393127,
            "question": "How often should a dry well be inspected and maintained?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.13457749783992767,
            "question": "How do dry wells help reduce flooding?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.07400818169116974,
            "question": "Can dry wells be used in residential settings?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.06583265960216522,
            "question": "Where are dry wells typically installed?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of Dry well is Stormwater management.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2906_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can dry wells be used in residential settings?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2906_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How do dry wells help reduce flooding?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2906_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How often should a dry well be inspected and maintained?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2906_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2906_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2906_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2906_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2906_144.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2906_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2906_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2906_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2906_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2906_93.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2906_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response to your query:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. According to the text, a dry well is used for stormwater management, reducing stormwater runoff and preventing flooding and erosion (see file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2906/re-ranker-msmarco/114.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement that the subject of a dry well is stormwater management. This can be inferred from multiple sources within the provided context, such as descriptions about how they collect and disperse excess water, manage stormwater runoff, contribute to groundwater recharge, and help prevent flooding and erosion."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}